There is more to fear than you can see.
Cube 2: Hypercube is a thriller, science fiction,
mystery film directed by Andrzej Sekula.
Eight strangers awaken with no memory, in a puzzling cube-shaped
room where the laws of physics do not always apply.
Kate Filmore, played by Kari Matchett.
Simon Grady, played by Geraint Wyn Davies.
Sasha, played by Grace Lynn Kung.
Max Reisler, played by Matthew Ferguson.
Jerry Whitehall, played by Neil Crone.
Mrs. Paley, played by Barbara Gordon.
Cube 2: Hypercube (stylized on-screen as Cube²: Hypercube) is a 2002 Canadian science fiction horror film directed by
Andrzej Sekuła, written by Sean Hood, and produced by Ernie Barbarash, Peter Block, and Suzanne Colvin.
It is the second installment in the Cube film
series and a sequel to Cube (1997).
Released in 2002, Hypercube replaces the colored industrial-style rooms
of the first film with high-tech, brightly lit chambers.
Instead of industrial traps such as flamethrowers and extending spikes, the rooms
have "evolved" to control illusions, time, space, and reality.
The film's critical reception was mixed, with reviewers panning the sequel's poorly produced CGI, writing,
and production, but praising its evolution from the first film, its acting, and its suspense.
The film explores themes of hacker, riddle,
detective, mathematics, claustrophobia.
The tone is mind_bending and thought_provoking and intense.